To put a stop to
ever-increasing corruption,
the legislative assembly votes
for a new anti-corruption bill today.
And waging a war against corruption is
our state's beloved Home Minister,
Satya Balram Azad.
The day our country is free from
all kinds of corruption and malpractices,
is the day I'll start
celebrating our Independence Day.
- Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
After you.
Good morning, Mr. Yashwant.
I hope the opposition will
not oppose this anticorruption bill.
Your father had the same attitude.
He too wanted to put an end to corruption.
But sadly, he met his end instead.
Don't let that Satyamev Jayate
[Truth Alone Triumphs] emblem fool you,
because the truth isn't
going to triumph today.
Not just opposition leaders like me,
but the people from your coalition
party too will vote against you.
Everyone, please settle down.
The house is in session.
As proposed by the
Honourable Home Minister...
The Anti-Corruption Bill Number
3381C is in session now.
All those in favour say aye.
- Aye.
All those not in favour say nay.
- Nay.
Nay.
Bill is not passed.
Mr. Speaker, please tell the Home
Minister not to be disheartened by this.
This is what you call... Democracy.
That's why our country is great.
Silence.
Please maintain discipline.
Honourable Home Minister,
you have two minutes
to address the assembly.
Roads are riddled with potholes.
Collapsing bridges
keep exposing fallen souls.
You got 100 bucks,
you got enough to buy a traffic cop.
If your name is Khan,
then you belong to a terrorist clan.
Yet they claim that our country is great.
Politicians use martyrs to seek votes.
Every leader wants credit
for Pilot Abhinandan's return.
Starving farmers keep hanging
themselves in their homes.
Yet they claim that our country is great.
People were shocked
when Tictok was banned.
But when it comes to rapes,
they say I don't give a damn.
What's trending on Twitter
is what's on our youth's minds.
Who cares about corruption, anyway?
Everybody's busy checking their
Instagram stories and wasting time.
Yet they claim that our country is great.
Home Minister Satya Balram Azad
had to face an embarrassing defeat today.
Let's go live to our political
editor Rashmi to find out more.
Ma'am, you voted against this bill.
How difficult was
it to make this decision?
Tell me something.
If you see two bills
lying in front of you.
A tenner and a c-note.
Which one would you pick?
Of course, the c-note.
I would pick both of them.
The tenner and the c-note.
The one who voted against
him in the assembly was a politician.
The one who proudly applauded
his speech was a wife.
Doctor...
Any change?
You ask me the same
question every day, Satya.
Your mother has been in a coma for 25
years because of that dreadful incident.
I don't think she
will ever come out of it.
I won't try to wipe away your tears.
It is sometimes better
to just let them flow.
Do you know why our
country is still great?
There are still some mothers left here
who give birth to men like you,
who always fight for the truth.
They lose, but they never stop.
And no matter what happens,
they don't break.
Dad, nothing except our currency
changed in the past 20 years.
The poor are still getting poorer.
Democracy is still
being taken for granted.
I am done losing my near and dear ones.
I vow to you,
now, either corruption ends
or the corrupt meet their end.
Don't forget to pray, okay?
Okay, Mom.
Let's hurry before they
close the temple for the day.
Hail Goddess!
Priest.
Sheetal.
Seek blessings from Mother Goddess
and pray that you do well in exams.
Shouldn't I first take
the blessings of my mother
who has worked so hard
to give me a better life?
Shee...
My baby.
- Let's go.
- Yo stumpy,
- how much did you make today?
- My exams are in the afternoon, Mom.
Don't worry.
- Not much, Dilawar-bhai.
- Why so less, huh?
Sheetal!
- Mom!
Sheetal...
Sheetal... please drive faster.
Please drive faster.
Fulfil our demands!
Stop, stop, stop.
Doctor...
- Fulfil our demands!
- Doctor...
Doctor...
My daughter fell down the stairs.
She is bleeding profusely.
- Please do something.
- Hey.
- Yes...
- Sir?
Step back.
Please don't do this.
- We came all the way here for treatment.
- We are on a strike, ma'am.
Your daughter won't
receive any treatment here.
If you want to save your daughter's life,
you better rush her to a private hospital.
Stop creating a scene
in front of the media.
What?
I am creating a scene?
You are the one putting
my daughter's life at risk.
We put you on the same pedestal as God,
because you can save lives.
When God doesn't have a right to strike,
who gave you that right, huh?
Mom!
Sheetal!
Sheetal, my baby, open your eyes.
I'll take you to another hospital.
Do you have some water, mister?
Keep your eyes open, dear.
Water?
Does anyone have water?
Sheetal, my baby?
Sheetal?
Open your eyes, dear.
I'll take you to another hospital.
Sheetal!
Sheetal, my baby!
Please God, don't be so cruel.
Sheetal...
Open your eyes, dear.
My daughter is dead.
She is dead.
Doctor.
Just like I couldn't
save my daughter's life today,
there will come a day when
nobody will be able to save your life.
Remember, sooner rather than later,
death will come for you.
Well done, Dr. Awasthi.
Your strike will sign the death certificate
of this city's Government Hospital.
I, Dean Agnihotri, will make millions,
but starting my private
hospital at its place.
[Humming]
You...
Hey you, why did you stop here?
Where are you going?
Hey bozo, I am talking to you.
You...
Hey bozo!
Where are you going?
I am talking to you.
This is not the time to visit a temple.
Can't you hear me?
Do you think I am crazy?
You...!
The police want to know my wrist size,
as they prepare to arrest me.
Hangman wants to know my neck size,
as he prepares to hang me.
And the corrupt get scared of
my guts when I beat them down to size.
Shit-scared.
Hey you, where do you think you are going?
All the doctors are on strike.
He won't receive any treatment here.
Go.
Take him to a private hospital.
Fact of life:
You reap what you sow.
What goes around comes around.
'This killer has proven that this
too could be a way to end corruption.'
'Our country has got a new hero.'
After Dr. Awasthi's shocking
and heart-wrenching death,
other doctors
and the government have
decided to meet halfway.
Jyoti Shrivastav,
who was never in the
favor of this strike too...
Ward boy.
As you can see, DCP Subodh Upadhayaya
just came here with his task force.
No criminal can escape
the law when I am in charge.
I'll start wearing bangles
if I am unable to handcuff them.
Dadasaheb had promised
to put an end to corruption.
That's the reason people
put us in power and made me the CM.
It's our responsibility to put an end to
corruption and not of some vigilante killer.
We will fulfil our responsibility.
I will fulfil this promise
and win the elections once again.
Perhaps then, we might be able
to convince you to join our party.
In your party, my identity would have
been restricted to being your daughter.
Now I can go head to head with both,
my father and my husband.
Politics is indeed in your blood.
That's because as a child, I spent
more time in your office than with Mom.
I saw the speech you made in the assembly.
Dadasaheb would have been so proud of you.
How is your mother doing?
I believe that she will
come out of it one day.
Then I will apologise to her,
for not being able to save Dadasaheb...
Papa.
I don't doubt your capabilities,
DCP Upadhyay,
but we need our best officer
to apprehend this killer.
I think I know whom
you are referring to, sir.
But he has been transferred several times
because of indiscipline
and disobedience issues.
Despite being a police officer,
he doesn't think twice before
taking the law into his hands.
I don't think this killer
is going to stop anytime soon.
Winds do not take long to become a storm.
And you need a rock to block a storm.
You approached the police to file
an eve-teasing complaint against me, huh?
Look at that.
Today, we celebrate Independence Day.
Today, I won't stop at eve-teasing.
Today, I will go ahead and touch you.
I know his methods flirt with the law.
Let me go.
But so deadly are his blows,
that the injured find no cure.
Let me go.
Hero makes an entrance.
Audience whistles and cheers.
Time for some action now.
You are an Indian woman.
You can give anyone hell
if you set your mind to it.
Hit him.
Stop.
Did I ask you to stop
streaming?
Keep shooting.
You are live.
It's time to prove your mettle.
Hit him.
Stop using your uniform
to flex your muscles, ACP.
We'd teach you a lesson for messing
with us if you weren't wearing one.
Why don't you just say that
you wish to see my body, huh?
It's not your fault.
This is what the public demands as well.
You don't need guts
to take a worthless life.
What you need is some
serious heavy-duty brawn.
He has stopped for the National Anthem.
What are you waiting for, boys?
Hit him.
Nation before self, always.
If you ever stop respecting women,
I'll make sure that you're left with
no option but to pee from your rear end.
Your tool will be rendered useless.
- Hail Motherland.
- Hail!
ACP Jay Azad is on his way here, sir.
He won't come here directly.
He will go somewhere else, first.
ACP has saluted the state's Home Minister.
Now can one brother hug another?
Since when did you start
asking for permission?
Since the time you got into politics.
How many times do I have to tell you that
you don't need to be so formal with me?
How can I not?
You are a minute older than me.
Not one, two minutes.
That's why I will always
stay two steps ahead of you.
And I will always chase you.
I'm a police officer,
it's a part of my nature.
Satya and Jay,
representing 'Satyamev Jayate'
[Truth Always Triumphs].
The two pillars of Dadasaheb.
A maker of laws and a protector of laws.
It's time to apprehend the person
who breaks the law as he pleases.
Both my handcuffs and my bullets
are eager to get to know him better.
Let's see who is he destined to meet.
Why have they queued up like this?
I am not holding an assembly.
Sir, they look like goats
queuing up before a slaughterhouse.
Don't you think?
- Hmm.
- Sorry, sir.
I usually don't answer
calls from unknown numbers.
You know it is a crime
to call and harass people, right?
Who says I am 'Unknown' to you?
I am the stranger
law has been looking for.
Hmm.
Every criminal thinks that
he can make the law dance to his tunes.
Only the one with guts can
make the law dance to his tunes.
Do you think you are a born vigilante?
I'll give every criminal
such a dreadful death,
that he'll refuse to be born again.
Your heavy voice and hard-core
dialogues don't make you Amitabh Bachchan.
Remember.
We don't need police from
11 countries to catch you.
Our police department is
more than capable of catching you.
I am doing this for our country.
If you really want to
do something for our country,
then you should become a part of the system,
become a police officer or a lawmaker.
Isn't your brother this state's minister?
Was he able to pass the
anti-corruption bill in the assembly?
The truth is that you cannot fight
this battle while staying in the system.
You need to have a
death-or-glory approach for it.
You get your shroud ready.
I'll keep your grave ready.
You know the Ashoka Pillar,
India's national symbol?
It can be proudly worn by
only soldiers guarding our nation,
and police officials like me.
Neither the President of India
nor the Prime Minister has that right.
I swear on the Ashoka Pillar,
I'll give up the right to
wear it if I am unable to stop you.
You are proud of the Ashoka
Pillar that adorns your hat,
whereas I am proud of the Ashoka Chakra
that lies in the centre of our national flag.
I am not scared of being
six feet under, Officer.
Even in my grave,
I shall salute our flaring tricolour.
- Hurry up.
- Calm down.
- Stop. Quickly shift him to one of the beds.
- Hurry up.
Doctor, please look
at what's wrong with Anwar.
- Move aside.
- My baby.
It's an acute case of food poisoning.
Nurse, start him on IV fluids stat.
- Please don't let anything happen to my son.
- Don't worry.
- I...
- Doctor, hurry up.
What's wrong?
Stop.
Madam, please tell me where
are these kids coming from?
All these kids were at the same place,
the Madrassa.
What is wrong with my son?
Why can't she breathe, Doctor?
Why can't she breathe?
Ma'am, this oxygen cylinder is empty.
Please do something, Doctor.
My daughter...
Ma'am?
- What do we do?
- Doctor?
Ma'am?
All the oxygen cylinders are empty.
Can't you see that all the kids are dying?
- Arrange for them, fast.
- She can't breathe.
Immediately.
Listen, I...
Excuse me.
We are out of oxygen cylinders, ma'am.
Use pumps, Amu.
- Okay.
- Amu, pump, fast.
Amu, pump!
Amu, use a pump, please, fast.
- Doctor, please save our son, Yusuf.
- Please save Yusuf.
Anwar!
40 kids at Anjuman Islam public
school suffered from food poisoning
after consuming food cooked
using expired food grains.
If that was not bad enough, all
hell broke loose on these little angels,
when the life-saving oxygen cylinders
in the public hospital they were taken to
ended up becoming the
reason for their death.
Anwar!
My baby!
Doctor...
Why is he here?
Are you here to shed crocodile tears
over our innocent children's dead bodies?
He knows that his people
are responsible for their death.
Today, he will pretend
to sympathise with us.
And tomorrow, his people will
ask us to prove that we are Indians.
He isn't here on humanitarian grounds.
He has a political
agenda behind this visit.
What are you waiting for?
Hit him.
Allah, I seek refuge in
You from the accursed Satan,
from his madness,
his pride, and his poetry.
This verse of the Quran
seeks Allah's mercy.
Do you want to give Islam
a bad name and make God angry,
by attacking an unarmed and innocent man?
We don't your sympathy.
We want justice.
Can you get us justice?
If you can,
then every father here will salute you
and every mother will bless you.
And if you cannot,
brother, I'll still pray
that to Allah to protect you.
Your wife's brother supplies the food grains
responsible for poisoning those kids.
And you had given the oxygen cylinders'
contract for Mahatma Gandhi Hospital
to your biggest contributors' company.
40 innocent kids are dead.
And you are enjoying
your tea and snacks here.
Chitchatting as if nothing happened.
- Hey!
- Oh, my God.
Mr. Satya,
you should not forget that you...
Tripathi.
He too needs to let the people
know how moved he is by this incident.
After all, Mr. Satya's party
gets the majority of their votes
from the people of the
same religion as those dead kids.
I think this happened for the best.
Ask me why?
Why?
Those kids would grow up and vote for Mr.
Satya's party.
Hmm.
So, the number of voters
and votes goes down by 40.
Oh, I see.
Who knows,
perhaps our party will come into power
in the future instead
of a coalition government?
100% right, Mr. Prasad.
I'll demand your resignation from the CM.
Hello!
Mr. HM?
Don't forget that you are the
Home Minister because of our coalition.
If I resign,
my whole party will follow suit.
I might not be physically strong
enough to break the table like you,
but I am politically strong
enough to bring your government down.
Brilliant idea, Doctor.
Right.
So what if the strike failed, huh?
This oxygen cylinder scam will surely
make the hospital shut doors for good.
And that will give
raise to our partnership.
A new, private,
Shankar Prasad Medical Institute.
Let's go.
- After you.
- By the way, where's Ms. Nora?
She will be here shortly.
"It's tough to survive."
"Now that you have stolen my heart."
"Look, this beautiful girl
is going crazy because of love."
"It's tough to survive."
"Now that you have stolen my heart."
"Look, this beautiful girl
is going crazy because of love."
"You are the cure for my pining heart."
"You are what my heart prays for."
"I am a sea and you are my shore."
"It's you..."
"It is your fault."
"It's me..."
"It's me who feels restless."
"It's you..."
"It is your fault."
"It's me who feels restless."
"It's you..."
"It is your fault."
"It's me..."
"It's me who feels restless."
"It's you..."
"It is your fault."
"It's me who feels restless."
"You are my love."
"You are my poison."
"Without you,
this life is nothing but a punishment."
"Take my name and come to me."
"Let me be known for my love as well."
"You are my prayers answered."
"You are also nothing but trouble."
"You are my journey."
"You are my companion."
"And you are my destination too."
"It's you..."
"It is your fault."
"It's me..."
"It's me who feels restless."
"It's you..."
"It is your fault."
"It's me who feels restless."
"It's you..."
"It is your fault."
"It's me..."
"It's me who feels restless."
"It's you..."
"It is your fault."
"It's me who feels restless."
"They pierce through my heart,
your mesmerising eyes."
"This hasn't happened just once,
but several times."
"There are many who are crazy about you."
"Some changed, some left
and some lost their lives for you."
"is poisonous."
"Your charms are deadly."
"You render me useless."
"You have such an effect on me."
"Your promises don't hold any value too."
"It's you..."
"It is your fault."
"It's me..."
"It's me who feels restless."
"It's you..."
"It is your fault."
"It's me who feels restless."
"It's you..."
"It is your fault."
"It's me..."
"It's me who feels restless."
"It's you..."
"It is your fault."
"It's me who feels restless."
"It's you..."
"It's me..."
Where the hell are you guys?
- "It's you..."
- "It's me..."
What? Who's dead?
Sir, he...
Turn the car around.
Turn the car around now.
Hey!
How did that fall?
Please.
Hey!
I...
No!
What are you doing?
Those innocent kids didn't know
that they were eating their last meal.
I am generous enough to let you know that.
This is the same food
those kids ate and died.
Now it's your turn to eat it.
No Satya, you cannot do this.
You are the HM.
HOME MINISTER!
We will confess our crimes.
You want us to resign, right?
- We will resign.
- Yes.
Now I will have you two resign from life.
Start feeding each other.
No...
I'll give you the same opportunity
you gave to those kids.
They are the same oxygen cylinders
that were available at that hospital.
They are empty.
What?
Right.
Don't worry.
You still have a chance to survive.
Those parents couldn't
save their children using this.
- Give it to me.
- Perhaps you might be able to save each other.
What was it that you two had said?
Good that those kids died.
They wouldn't have voted for your party?
Now neither Hindus nor
Muslims will vote for you.
No one can vote for the dead,
it's that true?
'Vigilante killer manages
to evade the police once again.'
'While Prasad and Tripathi's
death has disrupted the parliament,'
'public on the other hand celebrated it.'
'ACP Jay Azad has still not
been able to arrest the vigilante.'
Brother? You, here?
Why?
You look shocked like
you have seen a killer instead.
I am the one who was shocked.
I've been volunteering at the
children's ward for many years now,
but he never came to pick me up.
Today he shows up, unexpectedly.
By the way, what brings you here?
Vidya, the security guard
who can identify the killer
has regained consciousness.
So, he can give information
about the killer...
Officers, do you mind if I join you?
Hmm?
Sure.
- Vidya?
- Hmm.
Can you go home on your own?
Of course.
Sorry, but this is
a life and death situation.
Excuse me, Doctor.
We would like to talk to the patient.
- What are you doing?
- Please, Doctor, it's urgent.
Please.
Thank you.
Manohar Singh.
You saw him the other night.
The killer.
His face, his height, his body...
Tell us everything you remember.
My head is pounding.
Try to recall, Manohar Singh.
You will have to recall that night.
I didn't see anything.
I don't remember anything.
Try to remember.
Try to recall something at least.
This killer is quite clever.
He won't be able to identify the
killer even if he stands in front of him.
He might be clever but
not as smart as he thinks he is.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have made
the mistake of calling and challenging me.
He called you?
Yes, he must have called to scare him.
Did he scare you?
He should be scared.
He'll either get arrested
or die the day I get my hands on him.
And they are back.
They are carrying the Koran with them.
Why don't you go back
to your country, Pakistan?
Mind your manners, sir.
We are as Indians as you are.
My father fought
at the borders of this country.
You are making us run
in circles for his pension.
Would you like chocolate, dear?
Here.
You will feel happy
once you have the chocolate.
You need to make me happy.
If a bastard like you had
said this to your mother...
Would you give the same advice
to your mother as well?
Don't drag my mother into this!
Forget the pension.
Your daughter doesn't deserve
this chocolate either. Shoo.
Hey! What are you doing?
Let her go. I say, let her go.
Officer!
Vinayak.
Call the Police.
This officer needs to know
that he has no jurisdiction here.
Every part of India,
comes under my jurisdiction.
Baramulla's border comes
under my jurisdiction.
Rann of Kutch also comes
Fields of Uttar Pradesh
come under my jurisdiction.
The deserts of Rajasthan,
too, come under my jurisdiction.
My jurisdiction...
covers the whole of India.
This is not done.
I'll file a complaint against you.
Be my guest.
This country runs on politics
and favours, my man.
You can do me no harm,
my brother is
the Home Minister of this land.
You have 20 minutes.
If they don't get the pension cheque
by the time their prayers are over,
trust me, you won't find a place to hide
- neither six feet under,
nor in Pakistan.
Hurry.
Move!
Where's Abdul Hamid's file?
Abdul Hamid Sheikh.
Hurry.
Found it.
Give it to me.
Fatima Sheikh.
Spelling?
Hold your ears and squat.
A man who doesn't respect women
doesn't deserve to be called a man.
Women bring us into this world,
they need to be worshiped,
do you understand?
Here's a recap for those
who have just tuned in.
The Pride of Lucknow,
the newly constructed Gomti Nagar Flyover,
which was inaugurated by our
CM Chandraprakash Sinha, has collapsed.
We just learnt that Joshi constructions'
owner Maganlal Joshi
is about to issue a statement.
This...
This... happened because of the
sheer carelessness of the common man.
That child who is crying over there...
has lost his mother.
I want to ask his father...
what did he gain by breaking the law?
Why did he have to take
such a small child on the scooter?
Three people on a scooter
that too without a helmet.
Mr. Joshi, what would you like
to say about the allegations about
your company using downgraded cement?
All these allegations are preposterous.
Set up a commission, investigate,
and let them know that our construction
company is not responsible for this.
Mr. Joshi, I believe you
might be the killer's next target.
You just need to stay alert.
If you stay alert, you'll stay safe.
Target?
Why would anyone target me?
Mr. Maganlal,
act like a villain and vigilantes
are bound to come after you.
You are here to protect
me and not to crack jokes.
Mr. Maganlal,
don't get fooled by
ACP Azad's jovial nature.
My brother is the only one
standing between you and the killer.
My son is getting married.
We have the henna applying ceremony today.
Tomorrow, we will have a musical night.
The wedding and the reception
take place the day after tomorrow.
You should continue as planned.
If the vigilante attends
the wedding uninvited,
he'll be dead before
the wedding is solemnised.
HM, I'll be honoured if you
and your wife attend the wedding.
Thank you for your kind invitation.
We'll be there.
"I spent a year wearing
the same pair of heels."
"How about taking me
out shopping sometimes?"
"All my friends frequent beauty parlours."
"How about getting my black
hair highlighted sometimes?"
"How do I dress up for you?"
"All my clothes are old now."
"They are all worn out."
"I will get you an expensive dress,
my darling."
"What will I do with all my money?"
"I will get you an expensive dress,
my darling."
"What will I do with all my money?"
"Oh, my darling."
"You keep spending on your friends."
"Your wallet's empty
by the time it's my turn."
"Stay, where do you have to go now?"
"You always have some or
the other excuse ready to give me."
"Take me to a movie,"
"Or just spend some quality time with me."
"Tell me what's in your heart,"
"And I too will share
my feelings with you."
"I will get you..."
"I will get you an expensive dress,
my darling."
"What will I do with all my money?"
"Buy me an expensive dress, my darling."
"What will you do with all your money?"
"Oh, my darling."
"I stay sad when I am not with you."
"I keep chanting your name all day."
"You keep partying all
night with your friends."
"Then you blame me
for not taking you out."
"You are stingy."
"You are a miser."
"You always so grumpy."
"How about smiling sometimes, my darling?"
"I will get you..."
"I will get you an expensive dress,
my darling."
"What will I do with all my money?"
"Buy me an expensive dress, my darling."
"What will you do with all your money?"
"Oh, my darling."
- Hey...
- Oh no?
Power cut?
What caused this power cut?
Rastogi, go and check.
- I'll go and check. I'll go and check.
- Go, go, go.
Shukla.
Hello, sir.
Yes, sir.
Shukla, find out what
caused this power cut.
Yes, sir.
Rastogi is already on it, sir.
Hurry up.
Block the road stat.
Set up a barricade.
Everybody get ready.
SHOOT!
Hey!
What are you doing?
What...
Why do you want to kill me?
Don't kill me.
It's not my fault.
No Brother, Stop!
No, no, no.
No!
Told you, act like a villain and
vigilantes are bound to come after you.
Don't kill me.
Please don't kill me.
Don't forget the blood we share,
we've always made an amazing pair.
What happened?
I couldn't repay the money
I had borrowed from the moneylender.
So he took my buffalo.
How do I plough my
field without a buffalo?
How do I grow grains for my country?
This country is indifferent
towards farmers.
Farmers don't have anyone by their side.
Don't say that. You have God by your side.
And what if I don't even have that?
Then you have Dadasaheb
Balram Azad by your side.
He treats the earth as his mother.
He's the son of the soil.
With a weapon in his hand,
he becomes a warrior.
With a plough in his hand,
he becomes a farmer.
Weren't you supposed to go to Lucknow?
Weren't you supposed to
fast to get rid of the corruption?
What are you now, his buffalo?
You have managed to replace his buffalo,
but don't forget that his
plough is still mortgaged with me.
Never step on a lion's tail.
And never challenge Azad.
While the lion will just roar,
but Azad will tear your apart.
Run!
Scram!
- Dad!
It's nothing, Suhasini.
You call this nothing?
You are bleeding.
I'll get rid of corruption
from this country or I'll die trying.
I see.
So, you want to give all
your blood away for your country?
I'll save some for you.
- Daya kaka?
- Dadasaheb.
No.
I hope I'll be of some use
to you or your family one day.
Sardara, why don't you
do something about that cough?
How many times do I need to tell you?
I'll go get some tea for everyone.
Come, Sardara.
Dadasaheb, do you think
the Lokpal bill for which
you are about to fast in Lucknow
will end the corruption that's
been going on for 50 years now?
Perhaps my fast will ensure that no
one asks this question 50 years from now.
What are you two doing?
Let go of each other.
Let go.
Hey!
Chandraprakash?
Are you okay?
Yes, I am fine.
Kids were fighting.
I tried to break their fight,
but they pushed me away.
Please don't scold them.
They are just kids.
Why were you fighting?
Jay said that you and Mom love him more.
I am right.
You love me more, don't you?
This is no reason to fight.
We love you both the same.
Don't forget that you are my boys.
Hmm?
This world is a battlefield.
People will always try
to pitch you against each other.
If you fight each other,
the enemy always wins.
But if you join forces,
the enemy will always lose.
I hope the day they have to
fight against each other never comes.
"O' Mother..."
"You are my world."
"I want to gift you the stars."
- "O' Mother..."
- Dad?
- "You are my world."
- You'll fast from today?
Won't it be difficult?
- "I want to gift you the stars."
- It will be difficult. We are farmers.
No one knows the value of
food and grains better than we do.
Remember,
nation before self, always.
Dadasaheb.
"I will always keep
my country's pride intact."
"I will always be loyal to my country."
"I will die for you, O' my Motherland."
"Even the sky kisses
every speck of your land."
"I will die for you, O' my Motherland."
"My body, mind and soul...
belongs to my country."
"You reside in our hearts,
O' my Motherland."
"My body, mind and soul...
belongs to my country."
"You reside in our hearts,
O' my Motherland."
"This country belongs to partisans."
"Inebriated people live here."
"Bright sparks who'd lay down
their lives for their country stay here."
"We are the only one in this world,
"To address our country as Mother."
"Your soil... adorns my forehead."
"Accept my greetings, Mother."
"I will die for you, O' my Motherland."
"My body, mind and soul...
belongs to my country."
"You reside in our hearts,
O' my Motherland."
"My body, mind and soul...
belongs to my country."
"You reside in our hearts,
O' my Motherland."
"When tears well in someone's eyes,"
"When someone's being treated cruelly,"
"We will be for them."
"We are large in number."
"We cannot be defeated so easily."
"Your sons leave their homes,
it's time for glory or death."
"I will die for you, O' my Motherland."
"My body, mind and soul...
belongs to my country."
"You reside in our hearts,
O' my Motherland."
"My body, mind and soul...
belongs to my country."
"You reside in our hearts,
O' my Motherland."
"My body, mind and soul...
belongs to my country."
"You reside in our hearts,
O' my Motherland."
"My body, mind and soul...
belongs to my country."
"You reside in our hearts,
O' my Motherland."
Mom!
- Mom!
- Satya!
Jay!
Suhasini!
- Mom!
Stop!
Today is the 15th of August,
our Independence Day.
But is our country
really have any freedom?
No!
The day our country is free from
all kinds of corruption and malpractices,
is the day I'll start
celebrating our Independence Day.
What's the worst they can do?
Kill us?
Let the world know.
We treat the Holy Ganges as our mother.
We can do anything to
safeguard our motherland.
Long live Dadasaheb!
Students, teachers,
doctors, nurses, lawyers, police,
even government employees
all across the country
are supporting Dadasaheb Balram
Azad and his passive resistance movement.
This has been a peaceful protest, except
for a few reports of violence and riots.
We have heard that Chief
Minister Yashwant Paswan
is going to meet Dadasaheb today.
Dadasaheb is not happy with
the rising violence in the city
and the plight of the injured.
He has agreed to meet the Chief Minister.
You hid such a big thing from us, Sardara.
How could I say that that cancer
is slowly killing me?
I salute your courage.
You should stop fasting.
You are in a bad state.
Dadasaheb...
My country's state is worse than mine.
How can I get better before it does?
Brother?
Your sister insists.
You should stop fasting.
Please.
You have addressed me as Brother.
Then let me sacrifice
my life like a brother.
No.
Please... don't stop me.
Doctor?
You need to take him
to a hospital immediately.
I'll take him.
But Dadasaheb, CM will be here any moment.
If you leave...
Don't worry.
I'll take him to the hospital.
I'll take him there.
You keep making false promises.
You keep fooling us.
And now you want us to
calm down and listen to you?
I promise that I'll
introduce the Lokpal bill.
Dadasaheb! Dadasaheb!
Your wife Suhasini and Sardara
Singh met with an accident.
Blessed are those who
take the name of the Lord!
I'll make sparrow fight falcons.
I'll make cowards fight
like a brave soldiers.
I'll make one individual
fight against 125,000.
Only then will I call myself Gobind Singh.
Sardara!
What have you done, Sardara!
Dadasaheb,
since childhood,
there are two things
instilled in every True Sikh,
Gurbani [Guru's preaching]
and Kurbani [Sacrifice].
You've finally managed
to take your share of my blood.
Only those who aren't man enough
need two hands to get the job done.
Brave only need one hand
to deal with a bunch of cowards.
Dadasaheb!
Doctor!
Dadasaheb Balram Azad's war against
corruption ends with his painful death.
According to our sources,
Suhasini Azad is still
fighting for her life.
Dadasaheb's friend Chandraprakash
has made a declaration.
For every drop of his blood, I pledge.
I will form an Azad Party in his name.
We will contest in the next
election and fulfil his dream.
- Long live Azad Party!
- CM Yashwant Paswan was forced
to resign as his personnel
are accused of killing Dadasaheb.
Chandraprakash Sinha and his new
Azad Party will form the government now.
We will join forces and fight was one,
just as you wanted, Dad.
We take up the responsibility
of bringing the revolution
you dreamed of bringing here.
Sir, please.
Please give me some money.
Please give me some money, sir.
It is my fault that
I only burnt your face.
people would have given you more alms
if I had amputated your leg
like Abdul and thrown you on the streets
I am giving you one last chance.
Don't worry. He won't hurt you.
I'll give you my share of the money.
Here.
Take some more.
Santosh!
Someone help him.
Call an ambulance!
Heard about this one?
A beggar threw himself in front
of a moving car and committed suicide.
Why did he do it?
Because he didn't even
have money to consume poison.
You seem to be in a good mood, Shukla.
Let's go inside and
chitchat for a while, hmm?
Sure.
Why not?
Would you like a Paan [betel
leaf preparation], Shukla?
Yes, sir.
Banarasi, with betel nut slivers.
Awesome.
Go get Paans for Mr. Shukla.
Hmm?
There it is.
Hmmm.
Hey...
Actually, how about some
snacks before you have that?
Gyaaneshwar Chaurasiya.
Yes, sir?
Get some kebabs for Mr. Shukla.
I want to share a few jokes with him.
Hmmm.
Jokes?
Naughty jokes?
You thought the way
that child died was funny?
Now I will beat the crap out of you,
and you will laugh your heart out.
If you stop laughing,
and I'll start hitting you.
What do you mean?
Laugh.
Mr. Shukla is laughing like he's
enjoying a super hit movie's part two.
Why did you stand up?
You are reacting as if there
is an action scene going on in there.
It's not an action scene,
it's a comedy scene.
Sit down.
Start chewing it.
Did you enjoy it, Mr. Shukla?
How was the Paan, Mr. Shukla?
Fantastic.
What's wrong?
I guess the betel nut is too hard.
Sir, you never share jokes with me.
You never offer me any Paans.
I will.
I will offer them to you as well one day.
Wait for your turn.
Sir.
CM sir and commissioner sir want you
at the Lok Bhawan, urgently.
Okay.
Mr. Shukla, the kebabs I had
ordered for you are getting cold.
You should have them
immediately otherwise...
It's torn.
He's enjoyed the jokes
a tad too much, I guess.
No, Dilawar-bhai. No!
No!
Passive resistance isn't my thing,
brute force is what makes my heart sing.
Gandhiji is revered
as the father of the nation,
but Bhagat Singh is the one I take after.
- Rastogi?
- Sir.
Are you here to have Paan?
No, sir.
I am on duty.
I see.
Sir.
Hmm.
Hi.
Vidya?
Are we celebrating someone's birthday?
No, we are celebrating
Karwa Chauth [marital fast].
Karwa Chauth?
Hmm.
So, brother needs to be here.
So, if he is busy with some urgent work...
All urgent work can wait,
as the moon won't wait.
Yes, the moon.
Nor will my empty stomach.
He can act like the Home Minister
at the State Legislative Assembly,
but I am the Home Minister of this place.
Right.
If I am made to wait for
even a second more than necessary,
I'll have to set up a
big committee to investigate
and take strict actions against him.
Trapped.
What?
I mean he got trapped
after getting married.
That's why I prefer to stay single.
By the way, why isn't he here as yet?
He'll be here soon.
He couldn't dare to make you wait.
True.
- Hit him, brother!
- Hit him harder!
Why are you late?
Well, I... I...
It's okay.
There is still a lot
of time for the moon to rise.
Hello.
So, you finally got the time to show up.
Hmm.
You two make an amazing couple.
Jalebis! [Sweets]
Hmm?
What are you doing?
You are breaking your fast
before helping me break mine?
Of course,
how can I break my fast before you?
Hmm.
In fact, I too starve with you every year.
I mean fast.
I pray that everyone
gets a husband like him.
I pray that her husband comes back soon.
Huh?
You said something?
No.
Nothing.
No, no, no!
No!
Brother?
If anyone asks, we are three wise monkeys.
We see nothing.
We hear nothing.
Therefore, we cannot say anything.
Huh?
The moon will rise any minute now.
Where?
Huh?
He too will be here any minute now.
Who?
This.
- Huh?
- I'll be right back.
- Listen? Satya?
- So cute.
Vidya kissed me!
Grave sin!
Satya!
Satya, what have you been
doing in there for half an hour?
- I am fine.
- Satya!
The moon will rise any minute now.
How do I tell this moonstruck
that I am not her moon?
Satya!
Vidya?
I was waiting for you outside.
Let's go.
The moon will rise any minute now.
Satya, you?
Huh?
Jay, what are you doing in there?
But Satya had gone in there.
Vidya,
he visited it first.
I went to the bathroom after him.
Brother, wait.
You forgot this inside.
You see Vidya, we being
identical twins causes a lot of confusion.
We even have the same dimples.
Hmm?
I too have them.
Oh, so sweet.
By the way, when together you
two brothers can make anyone go crazy.
My job here is done.
Time for you to do yours.
"My eyes are very strange."
"They have seen a lot."
"But once they saw you,
they refused to look at anything else."
"My first passion."
"You are my first passion."
"You are my last love."
"You are my life."
"You are with me in my joys and sorrows."
"I held your hand to never let them go."
"Stay with me even
when my shadows leave me."
"To be honest,"
"My heart still beats for you."
"But once they saw you,
they refused to look at anything else."
"A pleasant evening."
"You are like a pleasant evening."
"You are like the moment of peace."
"You are my life."
"This is the state I am in,"
"Your love still keeps me awake at night."
"If anyone other than me gets
closer to you, I start feeling restless."
"My heart gets jealous,"
"Every time, you look at the moon."
"You are my life."
"You are with me in my joys and sorrows."
Long live Vidya Azad!
On this festive occasion of Durgotsava,
I would like to ask you all a question.
Mother.
Sister.
Wife.
Goddess.
Why is a woman's identity
restricted to these?
Why aren't many of them known Doctors,
Judges, Lawyers,
Chief Ministers and Prime Ministers?
If a woman can run a kitchen,
she can also run a country.
That's a lie!
Don't lie.
A woman isn't a mother,
a sister, a wife or a goddess here.
Tell me if you have been wronged.
I will help you.
You want to help me?
Fine.
Then give me back the honour
that was snatched away from me.
Rape...
I was raped.
Ibad Shaikh,
son of Aslam Shaikh, the textile king.
Randhir Kapadiya,
son of MLA Rajendra Kapadiya.
Virag Saxena,
son of the income tax commissioner,
Mahendra Saxena.
For now, these three have wronged me.
I used "for now" because the list
is going to increase in the coming months.
The DCP of the area where I was raped,
DCP Law and Order, Subodh Upadhaya...
He is Aslam Shaikh's lapdog.
He will refuse to register
my complaint saying,
You were raped a week ago.
Yes.
Were you waiting for
Christmas to complain?
He will ask for proof of rape.
I still won't give up and
file a court case against them.
On the day of the hearing,
I'll be attacked with knives and daggers
after I leave my house for the court.
They will stab me with iron rods.
Those three men will pour
kerosene on me and set me on fire.
No!
In this country,
whether you are Delhi's Nirbhaya,
Telangana's Disha, or an Unnao's daughter,
you will always meet the same fate.
If I am destined to
be torched after six months,
then why should I endure
their atrocities for so long?
Why don't I set myself on fire right away?
Someone stop her!
Doctor, please, save her!
She has serious burn injuries.
Please do something.
Please, Doctor!
She is seriously burnt.
Doctor, will this girl make it?
Arrest those boys.
CP, make Upadhyaya arrest them.
So that we can at least
clear out the accusations
that the girl has made against him.
We want justice!
We want justice for Jyoti!
What are you doing, DCP Upadhyaya?
Why are you arresting them?
Don't worry.
That girl will die in the hospital
even before they reach the jail.
Later, we will file
an appeal in the court
that they confessed under police duress.
Let's get going now.
Satya.
This girl shouldn't lose.
If daughters of our country
will give up like this,
mothers will be scared
to give birth to daughters.
Make this girl win.
Kill the ones who had wronged her.
And also kill DCP Upadhaya,
the one she knew would wrong her.
Women are done being trialled by fire.
It's time for you two to set things right.
I know the games you play.
I know what you two have been up to.
Enemies perish,
welfare accrues,
and the family rejoices,
for those who listen
to this glorification of mine.
Goddess Durga is here,
to slay the demons.
Glory be to the Goddess!
- Everyone together!
- Hail the Goddess!
Move it!
"This earth balances on Your trident."
"O' Goddess Mother,
this world is indebted to you."
"All evildoers get torched
by your bright light."
"So what if our tormentor is powerful?"
"Truth can pierce through anything."
"O' Goddess Mother,
these two brave sons of yours..."
"They will make sure that
all sinners pay for their crime."
"O' Goddess who rides the lion."
"O' Goddess of supreme powers."
"O' Goddess, unite me with my mother."
"Do it for this son
seeks his mother's love."
"I refuse to leave Your
doorstep empty-handed."
"O' Goddess who rides the lion."
"O' Goddess of supreme powers."
"Do the formidable."
"Let there be bloodshed."
"Kill all the demons."
"Do the formidable."
"Let there be bloodshed."
"Kill all the demons."
"I plead to you,"
"Shower your blessings upon us,
O' Goddess."
"O' Goddess who rides the lion."
"O' Goddess of supreme powers."
- "O' Goddess, unite me with my mother."
- Dadasaheb!
"Do it for this son
seeks his mother's love."
"I refuse to leave your
doorstep empty-handed."
"O' Goddess who rides the lion."
"O' Goddess of supreme powers."
"The one who rides the lion."
"The one who blesses all."
"The giver of light"
"Protect your devotees."
"Slay the sinners, O' Goddess."
"Bring them to justice, O' Goddess."
"Bless your devotees, O' Goddess."
"Answer our pleas, O' Goddess."
"Your earth is starving."
"Feed it some sinister blood."
"Use the sword of truth
to behead injustice."
"Take the form of ferocious Goddess Kali,"
"Get angry."
"Tear all the demons apart."
"Slay all the sinners once and for all."
"Slay all the sinners once and for all,
O' Goddess."
"Slay all the sinners once and for all."
"It's time for you to roar, O' Goddess."
"O' Goddess who rides the lion."
"O' Goddess of supreme powers."
Like every year, after two days,
on our father's death anniversary,
Chandraprakash will pretend
to offer prayers at Varanasi.
But this time,
he'll meet the same fate other
criminals have met from our hands.
When he gets the punishment he deserves,
his daughter will have tears in her eyes,
but the Azad family's daughter-in-law
won't even blink an eye.
I wouldn't be as calm as
you two are if my father's murderer
was sitting in front of me.
Dadasaheb wanted a
corruption-free country.
But I wanted position and power.
That's why I had to kill him.
Keep offering ghee to the fire else,
your mother will turn into ashes.
What did you think?
That I wouldn't keep an eye on that woman?
I made sure that I know the
moment she regains consciousness.
Now that you have seen
the Holy Mother Ganges,
it's time I take you to see your mother.
Satya...
Jay...
Hey!
Don't you dare!
What was it that your father used to say?
This world is a battlefield.
People will always try
to pitch you against each other.
If you fight each other,
the enemy always wins.
But if you join forces,
the enemy will always lose.
No!
I will win this battle!
That's why today is the special day when
you two brothers will fight each other.
And I will win.
That's why you two will
fight each other till death.
No.
No, Satya.
- No.
- And tomorrow,
I'll shed some crocodile tears and say,
"While doing his duty, Jay tried
to kill his vigilante brother, Satya."
"But both of them ended
up killing each other."
No.
They were survived by their poor mother,
who was in a coma until recently.
She has completely lost her mind now.
Fight each other if you
want to save your mother's life.
Fight!
They are done?
I'd expected you to birth to
a brave lad who'd last till morning.
Look at them!
You were so proud of your husband.
Call Dadasaheb Balram Azad!
Ask him to come to
save you and your children.
Call him!
Dadasaheb!
Come!
Save your wife and your children!
Call him!
Dadasaheb Balram Azad isn't just a man,
he is an ideology, he is a revolution!
As long as the sun rises,
Dadasaheb survives in us!
Look!
Look behind you!
They treat the earth as their mother.
They are the children of this soil.
With a weapon in their hand,
they become a warrior.
With a plough in their hand,
they become a farmer.
You want a brave lad, didn't you?
I have two brave lads!
Hey!
Satya! Jay!
Don't spare him!
Chandraprakash!
Mom!
Go, go, go.
Come on! Hurry up!
Brother!
Satya!
- Jay!
- Mom!
Let's go!
Mom...
Hit him, Jay!
Hit him!